http://www.gatesbbq.com/privacy-policy

$0.00
(0 items)
No products in the cart.
$0.00
(0 items)
No products in the cart.
Your Privacy is Important to Us
In this age of information, you value your privacy more than ever before, and so does Gates and Sons Bar-B-Q.
You deserve to know how Gates treats your private information gathered on this web sites.
We encourage you to read these paragraphs so that you can learn more about Raley’s web site privacy policy.
BY USING THIS WEB SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS WEB SITE PRIVACY POLICY.
IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT USE GATESBBQ.COM
Gates and Sons Bar-B-Q is committed to maintaining the confidence and trust of those who visit www.gatesbbq.com.
Gates and Sons Bar-B-Q is the sole owner of the information collected on this website.
Gates and Sons Bar-B-Q does not employ “cookies” in order to gain information about people visiting our website.
If you purchase a product or service from us on-line, we request certain personally identifying information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). When you enter your credit card number on our order form, we encrypt it using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.
After you submit a completed order form, you may receive a communication acknowledging our receipt of the order.
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or Social Security number) on our order or job application forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. But no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement here and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here.
